Not all damsels need saving.
Damsel is a western, drama, comedy film directed by David Zellner.
Oregon, a small town near the sea, around 1870.
Henry, a grieving man who aspires to preach as a way to overcome his unfortunate past, reunites with eccentric
pioneer Samuel Alabaster, who has hired him to officiate at his marriage to the precious Penelope.
What Henry ignores is that both must embark on a dangerous journey
through the inhospitable wilderness to meet her.
Samuel Alabaster, played by Robert Pattinson.
Penelope, played by Mia Wasikowska.
Parson Henry, played by David Zellner.
Rufus Cornell, played by Nathan Zellner.
Zachariah Running Bear, played by Joseph Billingiere.
Old Preacher, played by Robert Forster.
Damsel is a 2018 American Western black comedy film written and
directed by David Zellner and Nathan Zellner.
It stars Robert Pattinson and Mia Wasikowska.
The film premiered at the 2018 Sundance Film Festival on January 23, 2018 and was
released on June 22, 2018, by Magnolia Pictures and Great Point Media.
The film explores themes of black humor, alcohol abuse,
american wilderness, 19th century, far west.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.